interiorsbuyer.com 2011-12-04

# InteriorsBuyer.com - Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

InteriorsBuyer.com and its content is copyright of “InteriorsBuyer.com” (© “InteriorsBuyer.com” 2009/2010. All rights reserved.)

Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited other than the following:

  * you may print or download to a local disk parts for your personal and non-commercial use only
  * you may copy the content to individual third parties for their personal use, but only if you give this website as the source of the material

You may not, except with our express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the content. Nor may you sent it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system.

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how “InteriorsBuyer.com” uses and protects any information that you give “InteriorsBuyer.com” when you use this website.

“InteriorsBuyer.com” is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain datat by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. “InteriorsBuyer.com” may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.

You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any amends. This policy is effective from 1 November 2009.

We may collect the following information:

  * name, job title
  * contact information including email adress
  * demographic data such as post-code, preferences and interests
  * other info relevant to surveys and/or offers

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal records.
  * To improve our products and services.
  * To send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * To contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent illegal access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@InteriorsBuyer.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law.

Terms of Use

If you continue to browse and use InteriorsBuyer.com you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern InteriorsBuyer.com's relationship with you in relation to InteriorsBuyer.com.

The term “InteriorsBuyer.com” or “us” or “we” refers to the owner of the website.

The term “you” refers to the user or viewer of InteriorsBuyer.com.

The use of InteriorsBuyer.com is subject to the following terms of use:

  1. The content of the pages of InteriorsBuyer.com is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.
  2. Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on InteriorsBuyer.com for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.
  3. Your use of any information or materials on InteriorsBuyer.com is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through InteriorsBuyer.com meet your specific requirements.
  4. InteriorsBuyer.com contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.
  5. All trademarks reproduced in InteriorsBuyer.com, which are not the property of, or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the website.
  6. Improper use of InteriorsBuyer.com may give to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.
  7. From time to time InteriorsBuyer.com may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).
  8. You may not create a link to InteriorsBuyer.com from another website or document without InteriorsBuyer.com's prior written consent.
  9. Your use of InteriorsBuyer.com and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of Wales and England.
